ILGWU Archives Department Collected Publications 5780/121 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- In Der Arbeyter Welt, 1930-1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: In Der Arbeyter Welt, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    By The Day. Photocopies of a column from Der Tog, various dates. Item is in Yiddish.
- The International Kibitzer, 1934; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  v. X: no. Y (1934:June 2)
  - Item 1: The International Kibitzer, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    v.X:no.Y (1934:June 2). Item is in English.
- Joint Installation. Seating List, 1974; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hotel Roosevelt, New York City, March 30, 1974
  - Item 1: Joint Installation. Seating List, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Hotel Roosevelt, New York City, March 30, 1974. Item is in English.
- Local 23 News, 1963; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  v.6:no.2 (1963:June); v.6:no.2 (1963:Aug.)
  - Item 1: Local 23 News, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By Local 23. v.6:no.2 (1963:June); v.6:no.2 (1963:Aug.). Item is in English.
- Local 23-25 News, 1964-1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  English and Chinese.
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Local 23-25. Item is in English; Chinese.
- Der Morgen Zshunal, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Photocopies of two articles.
  - Item 1: Der Morgen Zshunal, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Jewish Journal and Daily News. Photocopies of two articles. Item is in English.
- The Organizer, 1933; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  English, Italian, and Yiddish. v.1:no.1,3-6 (1933)
  - Item 1: The Organizer, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Joint Board Dress and Waits Makers' Union. v.1:no.1,3-6 (1933). Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
- Report on Competitive Conditions as Affected by Transportation Cost in the Apparel Industry, 1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Report on Competitive Conditions as Affected by Transportation Cost in the Apparel Industry, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    By Wage and Hours Division. Item is in English.
- Der Shap Fartreter, 1922; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Der Shap Fartreter, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
- The Waist and Dressmaker, 1912; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  English and Yiddish. v.3-4 (1912). Very brittle.
  - Item 1: The Waist and Dressmaker, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    By Local 25. v.3-4 (1912). Very brittle. Item is in English; Yiddish.
- Vorwarts, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Yiddish. Photocopies of various articles.
  - Item 1: Vorwarts, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    By Forward. Photocopies of various articles. Item is in Yiddish.
- Miscellaneous articles in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Yiddish. Photocopies.
  - Item 1: Miscellaneous articles in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Photocopies. Item is in Yiddish.
- The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Photocopy
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By Evening Telegram. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By Tribune. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By New York American. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By Mail. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By New York Call. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By Seattle Union Record. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- The Public be Damned?, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- The Public's Business, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: $250,000 Union Fund to Defend Leaders Named by "Gunman", Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Public be Damned?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: This Is No Time to Stir Up Trouble, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Public's Business, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Protocol is Abrogated By Employers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Vote Aid for N. Y. Strikers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Freedom is Gained for Eight Unionists, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Garment Worker, 1972; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  v.15:no.9 (1972:Dec.)
  - Item 1: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Central Pennsylvania District. v.15:no.9 (1972:Dec.). Item is in English.
- Gerechtigkeit, 1940; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Yiddish. v.22:no.6 (1940:June)
  - Item 1: Gerechtigkeit, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.22:no.6 (1940:June). Item is in Yiddish.
- The Gestapo, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Gestapo, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Friends of Democracy. Item is in English.
- Heavy Ballot Halts Union: ILGWU Loses Election at Lawrence Mfg. Co. Plant, 1960; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  no.11 (1960:Mar. 17). Newspaper Extra Edition. Marked "Exhibit P" in pencil.
  - Item 1: Heavy Ballot Halts Union: ILGWU Loses Election at Lawrence Mfg. Co. Plant, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By Brunswick Times-Gazette. no.11 (1960:Mar. 17). Newspaper Extra Edition. Marked "Exhibit P" in pencil. Item is in English.
- Der Klouk Opereitor, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Yiddish. v.1:no.1 (1930:Dec.)
  - Item 1: Der Klouk Opereitor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By Cloak Operators' Mutual Aid Club. v.1:no.1 (1930:Dec.). Item is in Yiddish.
- Local 99 News, 1973; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Special Issue (1973:Jan.); v.16:no.6-9 (1973)
  - Item 1: Local 99 News, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Local 99. Special Issue (1973:Jan.); v.16:no.6-9 (1973). Item is in English.
- Local 105 News, 1973; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  v.4:no.4 (1973:Oct.)
  - Item 1: Local 105 News, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Local 105. v.4:no.4 (1973:Oct.). Item is in English.
- Ohio Kentucky News, 1972-1973; Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  v.8:no.4 (1972:Nov./Dec.); v.9:no.1 (1973:Jan./Mar.)
  - Item 1: Ohio Kentucky News, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    By Ohio-Kentucky Region. v.8:no.4 (1972:Nov./Dec.); v.9:no.1 (1973:Jan./Mar.). Item is in English.
- Our Union, 1973; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  v.22:no.46 (1973:Spring); v.22:no.48 (1973:Fall)
  - Item 1: Our Union, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    By Local 62. v.22:no.46 (1973:Spring); v.22:no.48 (1973:Fall). Item is in English.
- Our Union, 1984; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  v.22:no.81 (1984:Winter). 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Our Union, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    By Local 62-32. v.22:no.81 (1984:Winter). 3 copies. Item is in English.
- San Francisco Labor, 1966-1967; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  v.14:no.9-11 (1966:Feb.-Apr.); v.15:no.1-6 (1966:June-Nov.); v.16:no.1 (1967:June 9)
  - Item 1: San Francisco Labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    By San Francisco Labor Council. v.14:no.9-11 (1966:Feb.-Apr.); v.15:no.1-6 (1966:June-Nov.); v.16:no.1 (1967:June 9). Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1948; Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  January 1, 1948 - December 31, 1948. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published May 1949.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1948 - December 31, 1948. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published May 1949. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  January 1, 1953 - December 31, 1953. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published May 1954. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1953 - December 31, 1953. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published May 1954. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1954; Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  January 1, 1954 - December 31, 1954. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published April 1955.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1954 - December 31, 1954. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published April 1955. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1955; Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  January 1, 1955 - December 31, 1955. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published March 1956.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1955 - December 31, 1955. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published March 1956. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1956; Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  January 1, 1956 - December 31, 1956. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published March 1957.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1956 - December 31, 1956. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published March 1957. Item is in English.
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  January 1, 1957 - December 31, 1957. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published March 1958.
  - Item 1: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
    By Auditing Department. January 1, 1957 - December 31, 1957. Locals, Joint Boards, and General Office. Published March 1958. Item is in English.
- Justice, 1986; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  v.68:no.1 (1986:Jan.). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Justice, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.68:no.1 (1986:Jan.). Bound volume. Item is in English.
- Monatlakher Idisher Bulletin, 1929-1930; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Continued by Der Arbeyter Kamf. Bound volume containing both titles.
  - Item 1: Monatlakher Idisher Buletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    By Communist Party (USA). Continued by Der Abeyter Kamf. Bound volume containing both titles. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Der Arbeter Kamf, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    By Communist Party (USA). Continues Monatlakher Idisher Buletin. Bound volume containing both titles. Item is in English.
- Der Arbeter Kamf, 1930-1933; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Continues Monatlakher Idisher Bulletin. Bound volume containing both titles
  - Item 1: Monatlakher Idisher Buletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Der Arbeter Kamf, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Harper's Weekly, 1895; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  v.89 (1895). Bound volume. Brittle.
  - Item 1: Harper's Weekly, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    v.89 (1895). Bound volume. Brittle. Item is in English.
- Gerechtigkeit, 1924; Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Yiddish. v.6 (1924). Bound volume. Brittle
  - Item 1: Gerechtigkeit, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.6 (1924). Bound volume. Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.
- Gerechtigkeit, 1921; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Yiddish. v.3 (1921). Bound volume. Brittle.
  - Item 1: Gerechtigkeit, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.3 (1921). Boumc volume. Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.
- The New Post, 1915-1916; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Yiddish. v.4:no.283 (1915:Dec.) - v.5:no.334 (1916:Dec.). Bound volume. Brittle.
  - Item 1: The New Post, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    By Joint Board Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions. v.4:no.283 (1915:Dec.) - v.5:no.334 (1916:Dec.). Bound volume. Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.
- The New Post, 1917; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Yiddish. v.6:no.335 (1917:Jan.) - v.6:no.385 (1917:Dec.). Bound volume. Brittle.
  - Item 1: The New Post, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    By Joint Board Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions. v.6:no.335 (1917:Jan.) - v.6:no.385 (1917:Dec.). Bound volume. Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.
- The New Post, 1918-1919; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Yiddish. v.6:no.386 (1918:Jan.) - v.7:no.438 (1919:Jan.). Bound volume. Brittle.
  - Item 1: The New Post, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    By Joint Board Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions. v.6:no.386 (1918:Jan.) - v.7:no.438 (1919:Jan.). Bound volume. Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.
- The New Post, 1917; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Yiddish. v.6:no.368-370 (1915:Aug.-Sep.). Loose issues. Brittle.
  - Item 1: The New Post, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By Joint Board Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions. v.6:no.368-370 (1915:Aug.-Sep.). Loose issues. Brittle. Item is in Yiddish.